♬〜
(Male) This is fine.
(Male) Now...
♬〜
♬(Igawa) (humming “Hi Ho”)
♬(Humming “Hi Ho”)
♬Let's go home Let's go home I'm hungry
♬Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home
♬(Humming “Hi Ho”)
♬Let's go home Let's go home I'm hungry
♬Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home
♬Let's go home Let's go home
♬Let's go home Let's go home I'm hungry
♬Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home
♬Let's go home Let's go home
(Mitsuru/Takako) Hello, thank you.
Back from work? Yeah
(Mitsuru) Thank you for your hard work, Mr. Sudo.
Thank you for your hard work. Every day is amazing.
I walk 10,000 steps every day! amazing
That's too much
It's about 6,000 steps, but 10,000 steps is fine.
In that case, 5000 steps would be fine.
Why say less? But 70% more is terrible.
When I think back on it later
From "Ah, I walked 6,000 steps every day"
“I walked 10,000 steps” feels better, right?
What do you think?
Remember that lie, what should I do?
Well, well, well, well, even 6000 steps is amazing.
Because today...
It was 2000 steps
I really need to walk more because I'm young.
Yes, be careful, then be careful.
(Takako) Okay (Mitsuru) See you then.
Yes, thank you
(Ms.) Hahahaha
I'm home
(Mayumi) Welcome back
(Mayumi) I'm here.
(Mayumi) Ah yes yes
Hehehehe?
It's a video. Tell me first.
You know... Huh...
Yes, um... 5th anniversary. 5th anniversary.
Yeah yeah yeah
Well, I'd like to blow out the candle.
Are you about to turn it off?
Okay then let's go
Seno... (Sound of breathing)
Huh! (Mayumi) Yay
It's true, it's been 5 years so fast.
yeah? 5? 6?
We've been married for five years now, and today marks the sixth year.
I always end up not understanding this.
Hehe, I kind of understand.
So it's been eight years since we started dating?
Hey yeah
But it feels like a long time ago
Yeah, I'm sure.Which one?
No, you said it first, right?
(Mayumi) Ma-kun?
Aren't you tired?
Huh? what? that
Eh, I missed the answer.
Hmm...
Well, I might get bored if we stay together for another 100 years.
He's dead, no, no, I don't know.
It's impossible, right? 100 years.
Medical progress is amazing
So, is it okay if it's just the two of us for 100 years?
Peter is also there
I need Peter to live 100 years.
Hmm Peter, 100 years?
Is it tough? Hmm... Yeah.
Well then, get Peter a cute wife.
Peter Junior… Mayumi
I'm so happy right now
Mayumi is there, Peter is there
♬〜
enough as it is now
yeah?
♬〜
Hmm
Fufufufufu cream
copper?
Haha...
So sweet! Hahahahaha
It's attached (Mayumi) Is it attached? terrible
So sweet! So sweet!
(Mayumi) Noisy, noisy, noisy?
trip? Okay, not at all (Mayumi) Really?
Where do you want to go? (Mayumi) Yeah, where are we going?
I've never been to Hawaii... (Mayumi) I haven't.
Let's go (Mayumi) I want to go
That's fine (Mayumi) Yeah, Hawaii. I'm happy.
Here, Piotr, it's a snack.Here, Mayutr, please too.
(Mayumi) Looks delicious, huh?
(Mayumi)...Isn't that right, Peter? Eat a lot.
(Mayumi) What? what? Huh?
(Mayumi) What?
Since it's a great opportunity, there are three of us, including Peter...
Wow! (Mayumi) What?
Uso (Mayumi) Just do it properly.
You're doing it right (Mayumi) Really?
♬〜
(Female) Um... I've been forgetting things a lot lately.
(Watanabe) Ah, forgetfulness? (Female) Yeah
(Watanabe) By the way, what did you eat last night?
(Female) What did you eat? (Watanabe) Ah!
♬〜
Mr. Isomura's team and Mr. Sanada's team
From now on, draw the lottery in this box.
Please borrow what is written on that lottery ticket and bring it to us.
(All) Yes, the team that cleared all of them quickly.
It's a win
Yes, let's go...start
(Aina) It's the start, please be careful.
Please take it slow, take it slow, and make sure you don't get hurt.
here you are
Mr. Motomura, that's my breast pocket.
Please be careful, it's okay to take it slow.
(Isomura) Silver-rimmed glasses?
Isn't it black?
Silver please (Isomura) Yes.
yes yes
(Tada) What? what? Not very crowded
(Aina), Mr. Igawa suggested it.
I'm running a borrowed race (Tada). Wow, it's so nostalgic.
I did it a long time ago, but I've never done it before.
Huh? Me too, it's completely generic.
No, no, no, if you call it a generation gap.
Isn't Mukai-san on this team?
Oh, that's terrible, that would be harassment.
No, no, a different Mr. Takamori called "Gene Gya"...
I'm sorry (Aina) I'm too quick to apologize.
Please forgive me (staff) Tada-san.
We have a customer. Ah, that's it.
I'm a water server company.
Don't young people run borrowed goods races?
Ah, don't touch other people's things too much.
Is that the generation you grew up in?
Oh! (Rie) Newspaper Yes, okay.
Oh!
(Iida) Necktie Mr. Iida This is a towel.
Towel, no towel, out, out.
(Iida) stingy
(Aina) I'm going to the fair because it's a game.
(Iida) Oh, lend me that.
(Male) No... no, why?
(Male) You're not my enemy.
Look, I won't fight for a second.
Look carefully. It's a towel (Iida) Yeah.
(Rie) Iida-san's tie (Iida) Yeah.
(Rie) Please go find me (Aina) Are you okay?
Can I leave you here for a while? Ah yes
Mr. Tsukamoto
What was the topic?
Ah sneakers
It reminds me of when my daughter was born, haha.
first shoes
My mother-in-law over there bought it for me.
"Don't be silly!" I said, getting angry...hehe
I must have forgotten about my precious daughter.
(sigh)
(Hanae) It feels like my head doesn't belong to me.
I feel like this place is borrowed.
yeah? Ah...
Hehe I'll give it to you
Huh? Is that okay?
I'll forget that I made it anyway
About you too
you don't forget
♬〜
Understood thank you
ah…
Huh? yeah? What is this?
It's a borrowed race
Let's go look for sneakers (Hanae) Yeah.
Please be careful about the steps (Hanae) Yes, yes.
Good job hehe sneakers
♬Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home leaking pee Let's go home
⚟Thank you all for your hard work at work and housework today.
⚟The 21st and 22nd of every month are free regular check-up days.
⚟Don't forget everyone...
(Takako) Thank you for your hard work. Are you taking 10,000 steps today?
(Multi) 6000 (Takako) 10,000 steps
Hahaha (Takako) 10,000 steps, right?
(Mitsuru) Do you remember our conversation the other day? (Takako) I remember 10,000 steps...
Peter is home
Alright, it's a snack.
Ah... I have to buy it tomorrow.
Wait a minute, "Pyotr's snack."
Okay
Hey, it's a snack, Peter.
Are you full? Ah, I ate it
Is it delicious? Peter
Wow... Piotr hehe
Ah! Wait... a child?
Hmm, it's salty hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha Only for a good taste
Fufufufufufufufufu
Shame on you, what are you making me do?
(Mayumi) Hey, just stop. It'll disappear.
Hmm, the salt is good (Mayumi) I'm saying it again.
It's perfectly cooked (Mayumi) Oh, I'm so happy.
It was delicious and good
Ah, today, the resident Tsukamoto-san regained his memory for a moment.
Hey, does that happen often?
Well, sometimes
Well, how long does that memory last?
No, maybe from time to time
Sometimes it lasts for a moment, sometimes for 5 minutes, sometimes for hours.
I see.
Did you get this from (Mayumi) Tsukamoto-san?
Yeah, I made it during craft time last week.
"Don't forget about me"
It's kind of hard...
But forgetting
I started to think that it's not all bad.
Is that so? Yeah
Well, I forget the happy things too
Because I can forget the hard things
Is there one? It's so painful that I want to forget it
No (Mayumi) What?
Fufufufufufufufufu
You're happy
Ah, then...
(Mayumi) Yeah...
Even if you hate me so much that you want to forget about me
I'll put this here so I don't forget
Hahahaha What? There's no way that's the case.
Ah, you said something nice.
I'll give you 5,000 yen of your pocket money! Yay!
(Mayumi) Hahahahaha
♬〜
(Mayumi) Kya!
Mayumi?
Huh... Ma-kun, Peter...
♬〜
Because I... left the window open...
(cry)
It's not Mayumi's fault
♬〜
Ah... good morning
(Takako) Good morning.
♬〜
(Aina) Igawa-san, are you okay? Huh?
(Aina) No, I'm not feeling well today.
Ah... no, it's okay
Oh, did you have a fight with your wife?
No... my pet sparrow died.
Eh...
Maybe there's a stray cat in the middle of the night...
That's... I'm sorry.
I have a cat, right?
Sorry
No... it's fine, nothing special
I don't hate all cats
Free medical examinations are coming, so please go when you are free.
got it
(Aina) Do you want to see the photo? my cat's
why? (Aina) This
So cute... Thank you (Aina)
Wow, even if I could just get a free checkup every month.
It's worth moving to Morinuma.
That's right, yeah
(Checkup staff) Thank you for your hard work.
Next person please, yes please
(Doctor) Masaki Igawa, yes.
(Doctor) Now, please lie down there.
♬〜
(Doctor) Yes.
Well then, I'll look into your eyes.
(notification sound)
(sigh)
♬〜
Ah...
Ugh...
♬〜
Ah...
Ah... ah...
ah…
(breathing heavily)
Ah...
♬〜
(electronic electrocardiogram sound)
Teacher, I'll call you!
Why are you here?
He was found lying on the riverbed.
You were brought here, don't you remember?
Do you know your name? I'm Masaki Igawa
He was found without any ID or cellphone...
OK? Yes, I'll give my wife a call.
yes…
♬〜
Huh? Excuse me, is today June 28th?
yes
(Ring tone)
Please take me to Morinuma-cho (driver).
(sigh)
thank you
(chime)
yeah?
Mayumi?
(cry)
yeah?
ah…
(sound of breathing)
♬〜
(cry)
ah…
Huh?
５Ｌ？
why?
♬〜
(Sound of door opening) (Mayumi) Hehehehe
Hey, it's completely different than I thought.
(Tada) It's supposed to be a love story, right?
That makes me too hungry.
(Mayumi) Hehehehe there? (Tada) That's right.
why? (Tada) No, I really did.
Hahaha, as expected (Mayumi) from a while ago
All they say is "I'm here"
(Tada) I couldn't understand numbers 1 to 10.
(Mayumi) Hehehe, it doesn't mean you don't understand anything.
(Tada) I didn't understand so much that I got distracted during the process.
That's the kind of movie it is (Mayumi), isn't it?
Hey, thank you for this (Tada) You have to indulge once in a while.
(Mayumi) I'm so happy... Huh? what? suddenly
(Tada) Come on, let's kiss (Mayumi) Here?
(Tada) Quickly, quickly, quickly, leave it once (Mayumi) No more.
Hey, if you don't apply this first, it will wrinkle...
(Tada) Yeah, it's not really "hehe"...it's true.
Huh?
It seems like something is stuck...
Huh? which one? Huh!
Is something stuck inside? (Mayumi) Yeah
Maybe something I was stacking fell and got stuck?
Wait a minute, huh! Huh?
Huh?
(Mayumi) What do you think? (Tada) Hmm...
Ah... no, I might have to remove the whole door.
(Mayumi) Eh? (Tada) Where is the tool box?
I think it's on the shelf in the entryway.
(Tada) Well then, let's sort out the things we don't need.
♬〜
(Tada) Hmm... (Mayumi) Is there?
(Tada) Ah, there, there.
Yeah
♬〜
(Tada) Okay...
It's just a matter of what to do with this.
(Mayumi) Huh? Huh?
It's open (Mayumi) Why?
(Tada) Ah, but I wonder if this is what caught me?
(Mayumi) Which one?
♬〜
why? Since when?
(Mayumi)《What... what? what? 》
ah…
That's a lie...
Huh?
♬〜
(Security guard) May I see your ID?
Ah, I have it in my hands now...I dropped it.
Ah, Mr. Mukai
Sorry, I was in the hospital for a week after the accident.
Are you meeting someone? yeah?
If so, please accept
(Security Guard) May I ask the resident's name?
Oh, no, no, I'm a staff member here.
Mr. Mukai
Um... which one are you?
Huh? Please wait
What kind of joke are you kidding? It's Ikawa.
Ah, Mr. Igawa
♬〜
what happened?
This person said that he was ``Igawa.''
What do you mean? Now… “I work here.”
Um... Igawa is me, but what about you?
What is Tada-san saying?
There's more to the story than that.
please wait a moment
Since when is Mayumi?
Huh? Why are you pretending to be me?
What's so funny? Hey!
(Security guard) Could you come with me?
Wait, what? (Security guard) No, just a moment...
Ah, Mr. Isomura! You understand me, right?
This is Ikawa
Hey, it's the police. Police (security guard), hey... it hurts.
Chase me! quick! Ah... wait!
♬〜
Huh?
I know you're saying something strange.
But no one remembers me.
I was in the hospital for a week and no one seemed to care.
On the contrary, someone else is pretending to be me.
I don't understand...
So who am I? That's it
please calm down
Oh... am I crazy?
The MRI showed no abnormalities.
Do you have anything left to prove your identity?
So you're saying you lost everything!
Sorry
(Sawai)《I saw him lying on the riverbed.
It was discovered...》
"(cry)"
(Tada)《Let's kiss.》
♬〜
《Which one are you? 》 (Tada)《Igawa is me》
(Yuri) I'm sorry.
♬〜
(brake sound)
OK?
Please help!
Please ride! yes!
♬〜
(Tsumura) Ah...
OK?
Ah sorry thank you
My son caught a cold.
So I was thinking of getting some medicine and going home.
You jumped out...
Did something happen?
No...I don't quite understand it myself...
I had an accident about a week ago.
Huh? So I was taken to that hospital...
When I woke up, no one remembered me...
Someone else is pretending to be me at work
My coworkers also thought that person was me...
I don't really understand what it is
What about your wife?
Huh?
You are married, right?
♬〜
Did you meet your wife after the accident?
home…
♬〜
I'm sure your wife will be fine.
There's no way I'll forget someone important to me
♬〜
I found Ikawa
Mr. Kosaka...
♬〜
Thank you no
that…
♬〜
Please contact me if you have any questions
thank you
♬〜
(chime)
Hello, I'm home now
Sorry I'm late
It's okay, Kento is already asleep.
♬〜
thank you
📱(Osamu) Take care when you go home
that…
📱(Osamu) What happened?
♬〜
Mayumi...
no…
Kento: Did you eat properly?
(Haru) Yeah, I had two refills of rice.
Hehe, I see.
Which one are you?
♬〜
No one remembers me, so who am I?
(Tada) What are you doing there?
What do you mean by barging into my house?
My husband was in an accident two years ago...
They really look alike.
(Tada) Don't believe what that man says.
You have no relationship with Masaki Igawa.
that person killed someone
should not be tolerated for any reason
Let's look for more people who remember Mr. Igawa.
I love Mayumi and that's enough